GUNJALI KRISHNA

Banking/Insurance/ Sales & Leadership

SKILLS

Marketing & Sales Professional Insurance Specialist. Leadership Role & Team Handling Digitalization NBFC &Banking and Finance

AWARDS & HONORS

State level Qualified Marathon Runner. Internship

COMPUTER PROFICENCY

Word 2010 Excel 2010 Power Point 2010

LANGUAGES

Hindi

- .

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

PGDM (International Business & Marketing)
CAT Qualified-89% MAT
Qualification-92%

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Yoga

PROFILE

A financial services professional with 12+years of diverse experience across different facets of fintech, Consumer Banking & corporate sales.

Digital & Product management, analytics, branch operations, P&L Management.

Handling retail branch Banking & Insurance for Gurgaon and Delhi. I leverage my Marketing and Insurance Expertise to Drive Business Growth, Customer Satisfaction and Delight. I drive products of financial domain which includes Salary/Banka Insurance catering different needs ofcustomer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Policy Bazaar.com

Jan 2024-Current

- Joined PB Fintech Limited as SBU Head Retirement sharing expert insights on the dynamic realm of Insurance of India.
- For Envisioning the future trends in insurance 2.0 and playing a transformative role in simplifying the insurance buying process, enhancing accessibility bridging the digital physical gap shaping the financial future of all who are planning to retire planned and secured.
- Managing a team of 55 Advisors and 4 team leaders with a deputy manager of retirement span of PB and day in day out target vs Ach for the entire Investments for Appointments.
- Keep a track of outbound calls and follow-ups with potential customers to present Policy Bazaar Investments plan and products. Handle inbound inquiries/ Escalations of the customers interested in Investment product and provide comprehensive solutions.
- Train the team to understand customer investment objectives, risk tolerance, and financial circumstances train them to recommend suitable investment solutions.
- Auditing the internal calls to check that all customers queries, concerns and objections are addressed
 effectively, and provide exemplary customer service.
- Plan & Execution to achieve sales targets by getting more leads converted in successful sales. Look into the call quality of the team to adhere to the company policies, procedures and ethical standards while conducting entire sales experience.
- Stay up to date with latest investment products and contribute to overall success of the team. Taking interviews as and when required.

AVP-Corporate Salary - KCM

Jan 2023- Dec 2023

HDFC BANK

Delhi & Faridabad

Delhi & Faridabad

Gurgaon, Haryana

- Achieve the NTB and Cross Sell targets and Insurance for the various Corporates.
- Management of existing portfolio of approximately 350 Cr for the corporation.
- Hiring Sales Managers/KAO as per the Team Requirement.
- Deepen the relationship by Cross Selling Bank products and Services, according toarising need of the corporation.
- To Enhance and Retain customer profitability, by capturing large share of Walletof existing customers.

AVP-Corporate Salary

November 2021 – January 2023

YES BANK

- Team Management to achieve the NTB and Cross Sell targets.
- Management of existing portfolio of approximately 300 companies
- Hiring Sales Managers in align with Hr. policy. (Team Size-240)
- To Ensure profitability of portfolio: Generate high income per customer along with their insurance customized Solutions.
- To access and resolve the operational and service queries/grievances.

Senior Manager-Corporate Cards

November 2016 - November 2021

ICICI BANK

- Onboarding of Corporates /MNC/PSU etc. for T&E, B2Band CTA of paymentSolution.
- Has built the most profitable portfolio T&E and CTA portfolio at NCR Level.
- Focus on Marquee and rated clients, with a high sanction value of Credit limits.
- Maintaining Synergy with multiple stake holders such as LCG. GCG, MNCs, PSUs,TXB, SMEG etc. to achieve goals & maximize card-able expenses and generate higher revenue.
- Profiling Corporate, meeting the owners/decision makers, assessing their currentbilling potential and future possible requirements, by meeting the decision makers.

.

PROJECTS UNDERTAKEN

As part of PGDM curriculum

Project Title: Market Research on Rails manufactured By SAIL and Global SteelTrade Analysis

PERSONAL INFORMATION

April 22, 1988 Birthday

Female

Gender

Married
Marital Status

Indian

Nationality

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager-Corporate Salary

ICICI BANK Noida, Delhi

- Acquisition of Corporates in alignment with the banking needs of Salary accounts and other products Like Motor Insurance (Team Size-145)
- Identifying and catering the various needs of the customer by providing them different solutions like credit cards, personal loan, SIP, Mutual Funds, Car Loan, Home loan, FD, RD, Insurance, family savings accounts etc.
- Handling a team of sales officers, held responsible for their acquisition and expansion of the current banking portfolio.

Manager-Corporate Salary

Kotak Mahindra Bank

Gurgaon, Haryana

- Onboarding of Corporates /MNC/PSU etc. for T&E, B2Band CTA of paymentSolution.
- Meeting CFO'S or decision maker to initiate the decision for bankingrequirements.
- Providing Solutions to corporates in cost cutting, beneficially with Kotak productand services.
- Team Handling of 8 sales Managers along 62 Deputy Mangers and AssistantManagers with and to align them to achieve the KRA's.
- Conducting various marketing Activity to drive sales Numbers.

Assistant Manager

Times job (Times Business Solution Limited)

Dec 2014 –June 2015

Gurgaon, Haryana

- To set and achieve primary and secondary sales targets for the Area.
- To train, motivate and lead the team towards the achievement of sales and distribution objectives.
- To plan, build and maintain distribution network in Area, to ensure optimum distribution.

Sr. Sales Manager & Business Executive

Sept 2013 -Dec 2014

Power Wind Ltd (R.S. India Group Pvt. ltd.)

Udyog Vihar, Haryana

- To set and achieve primary and secondary sales targets for the Area.
- Handling prospects and Clients in India and aboard so to assist and close the deal.
- Team Handling to ensure their alignment with Company Vision.
- To conduct market research and survey in India and Abroad in alliance withproject coordinators.

Product Trainee

June 2012 - June 2013

Roche Diagnostics India Pvt Ltd

Udyog Vihar, Haryana

Product Trainee/ Virto Diagnostics

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

PGDM-Balaji Institute of International Business,

BSC-Andhra University, Visakhapatnam

SSC/HSC-St. Xavier's School, Bokaro Steel

City (Jharkhand)

2010 – 2012

2007- 2010

2007